This is Alfa 13
这里是阿尔发13
The base, please answer
基地请回答
This is the base. What's the current situation?
这里是基地目前情况如何
We were attacked by the enemy during the task
任务进行中受到敌人的袭击
Among 324 people in the Alfa troop
阿尔发部队324人中
323 people were killed in the war
323人阵亡
I am the only survivor
生存者只有我一人
Enemy…
敌人…
Should be the Union
应该就是Union
What's up?
怎么回事
What was it just now?
刚才的是什么
The base, please answer
基地请回答
This is Alfa 13
这里是阿尔发13
Please answer
请回…
Go this way. Move quickly
往这里走, 动作快
Help
救救我
Where are you going?
你要去哪里啊
Play more with me
再多跟我玩玩吧
Heck. It's not even enough to pass the time
真是的, 连打发时间都不够格
Sorry to interrupt you
抱歉打扰你的休闲时间
Target doesn't seem to be there
目标似乎不在那里
Found it
找到了
Tazio
塔基奥
The location of the apron was sent to you
停机坪的位置传送给你了
It's a little far away from you. Can you rush over?
离你有点远, 能赶过去吗
No problem
没问题
Damn it
可恶
Target has been captured
目标已捕获
I want to say that we haven't had a big task for a long time
想说很久没有大任务了
Just this extent
居然就这点程度
Shark, sledgehammer
鲨鱼, 大锤
The task doesn't exist to satisfy you
任务并不是为了满足你们而存在
Our Captain Kleis is here
我们的克莱斯队长大驾光临了
Tazi
塔奥
Tazio
塔基奥
The backup force will take charge of everything here
这里交给后援部队负责
We will move to the next task place
我们往下一个任务地移动
Where is the next task place?
下一个任务地在哪里
Japan
日本
Something that must be guarded
(必须守护的东西/Ordinary)
I actually want to get to school early
我居然会想早点到学校
This is the first time since I was born
这还是我出生以来的头一遭
Because the days in hospital make you feel bored
因为住院的日子让你闷得慌
But Little Yu, you might as well take more rest
不过小裕你还是多休息一下比较好吧
That hand of you can't copy notes
你那只手连笔记都抄不了
That hurts
好痛
What are you talking about?
你胡说什么
Xue, you may as well copy it for me
学你帮我抄不就得了
I can only agree with you
真拿你没办法
Is it true or false?
真的假的
It's the first time I meet him
第一次见到
Who's he
他是谁
What's wrong
怎么回事
Girls' eyes are showing love
女生的眼睛都在冒爱心
I don't know who he is
不知道是谁
Is he the new guard?
是新来的警卫吗
Good morning
早安
Morning
早安
Your hand
你的手
I had a car accident not long ago
我不久前发生车祸
He is always reckless
他老是冒冒失失的
I did it to save you
我是为了救你耶
Sorry. Sorry
对不起对不起
Master, it seems that the memory remove was successful.
看来记忆清除顺利成功了, 主人
Who the hell are you?
你到底是什么人
So was the couple we took out
我们解决掉的那对男女也是
They are obviously not ordinary humans
他们很明显不是普通人类
We belong to the organization "Union"
我们隶属于"Union"这个组织
Union
Union
is an organization with super-standard scientific capabilities
是拥有超水准科学实力的组织
It can be said that we are their works
我们可以说是他们的作品
Having said that, I'm just an experimenter
话虽如此我只是个实验体
Just for them to complete the finished product like Jack and Mary
只是为了让他们完成像杰克和玛莉那样的成品
I couldn't even do this level of things at first
刚开始我连这种程度的事都做不到
However, as time goes by
不过随着时间增进
I don't know why only M-24 and I
不知为何只有我和M-24
have completed the special evolution
完成了特殊进化
Well
说是这么说
compared to the finished product
但跟成品比起来
We are like scrap metal
我们就像是破铜烂铁一样
The experimenters like you
跟你一样的实验体
So many people
还有多少人
have passed away
已经都不在了
I am the only one who survives
存活下来的只剩我一个
I couldn't even save M-24
我连M-24都没能救成
What do you plan to do in the future
今后你打算怎么办
If you have nowhere to go
如果你没有地方去
You can live here
你可以住在这里
You rebelled against the organization
你反抗了组织
If you are found alive, you may be killed by the organization
要是被发现你还活着可能会被组织追杀
What's your attempt
你有什么企图
You protected my students
你保护了我的学生们
They were only slightly injured
他们之所以只有受点小伤
It was because of you and your friends
是多亏你和你的朋友
Of course, if you want to leave, you can go
当然你如果想离开的话 你尽管离开
I have no plan to lock you up
我没有把你关起来的打算
Is what you said true?
你说的是真的吗
You trust others so easily
你这么容易就相信人
But I'm not as kind as you
但是我可不像你们一样好心
Things like trust are not important
信赖之类的并不重要
Only master's decisions are important
重要的只有主人的决定
But this is not for you to benefit for no reason
但是这可不是让你平白得到好处
It's just that I'm looking to increase my staff
刚好我正想增加人手
Frank
弗兰克
Yes, master
是, 主人
I'm going to school
我去上学了
Give me that
那个给我
Could it be that…
难道说…
Will the master intend to practice what I taught him last night
主人打算实践我昨晚教他的那个吗
Good morning
早安
Hi, long time no see
哟, 好久不见
Well, catch him
好, 抓住他
Wait, what are you doing?
等等, 你们干嘛啊
Come on
别这样
Look over there
快看那边
It's Leggiero
是莱杰罗同学
He's so handsome
他好帅啊
Good morning, Lai
你早啊, 莱
Long time no see
好久不见
How are you recently?
过得还好吗
(Fractured man, satyr, fool)
(骨折人 色狼 笨蛋)
What's wrong?
怎么了
Do you think this is rare?
你觉得这个很稀奇吗
Does Lai want it?
莱也要吗
Sure enough, this would make people want to doodle
果然会让人想涂鸦
What the hell is it?
这什么鬼啊
Don't doodle
不要给我乱画
Really? this is so cute
是吗, 这很可爱啊
This is not cute
哪里可爱了
Little Yu's face is fierce. So it's really six of one and half a dozen of the other
小裕脸长得很凶正好半斤八两啦
What's your meaning?
你什么意思啊
You don’t know if the host is still having fun?
不知道主人玩得还开心吗
You little Yu
你真是的, 小裕
You can’t use your mobile phone in class
上课不能用手机啦
Lai, don't you eat it?
莱, 你不吃吗
I'm waiting for it to expand
我在等它膨胀
Why are you here again?
你怎么又来了
What does it matter?
有什么关系啊
I just play with my friends for a little while, and then I will go back home
我只是跟朋友玩一下就回家
OK, see you
好, 挂了
See you tomorrow. Bye
-明天见 -拜拜
It finally came to an end
终于结束了
Xue, did you buy the one published before?
学, 之前出的那个你买了吗
Game?
游戏吗?
I bought it
我买了
Fantastic
太好了
We must pass the game
今天一定要破关
You still want to play with your hands like this?
你手都这样了还想玩啊
Lai, if you are free, do you want to come to my house together?
莱你如果没事的话 要不要一起来我家啊
It's a good idea
这点子好
But you are weak in playing games
可是你游戏打得很烂
I'll give you special training
我来给你特训
What's wrong with you?
你怎么了
Isn't is convenient?
不方便吗
You live in the chairman's house, right?
你住在理事长家对吧
Right
对喔
If you go to other places without explaining, the chairman will worry, right?
要是没交代就去其他地方 理事长会担心吧
And you don't have that
而且你也没有那个
You are right
就是说啊
How did you feel on the first day at work?
工作第一天感觉如何
Nothing special
没什么特别感想
I just provide labor in exchange for food and lodging
我只是提供劳动力换取吃住而已
And I don’t know how long it will last
而且我也不知道能持续多久
Really?
是吗
Frank
弗兰克
This world really changed
这个世界真的变了
Master, because the time you slept
因为主人您沉睡的时间
is too long
实在是太漫长了
The humans are fantastic
人类真是了不起
Those kids have things I don't have
那些孩子们拥有我没有的东西
They said
他们说了
If I have that thing
如果有了那个东西
I can do more
我就能做到更多事情
I will not go the wrong way
不会走错路
Occasionally, I can make a long detour sometimes.
偶尔也能够绕点远路
And we can play game if we have that thing
有那东西还能玩游戏
Master, are you talking about the cell phone?
主人是在说手机的事情吗
I'm very sorry
真是十分抱歉
I will prepare it for you immediately
属下立刻为您准备
Good morning
早安
Good morning, man
早啊, 叔叔
Man
叔叔
Hope you work well
希望您工作顺利
Bye, man
掰啦, 叔叔
Lai, good morning.
莱, 你早啊
Is this the cell phone?
这不是手机吗
Does Lai have a cell phone?
莱有手机了?
This is the latest model
这是最新型的
Then you don't need to answer the phone through the chairman
这么一来你就不用透过理事长接电话了
Tell the phone number to me
把电话号码告诉我吧
Don't you know the phone number?
你不知道号码吧
Then it's my turn
那就轮到我出手了
Lai, lend me your cell phone
莱, 手机借我一下
I will teach you how to become a master of smartphones
我来教会你怎么成为智慧型手机大师
First, like this.
首先要这样
And then, like that.
然后这样
Xue, send my number and mailbox address
学, 把我的号码和信箱地址传过去
This is called email
这个叫作电子邮件
As long as you do this
只要这样做
You can use emoticons and kaomoji etc.
你看就能使用表情符号和颜文字之类的
(The prisoner held explosives and committed suicide while fleeing)
(犯人持有爆裂物 逃亡中自杀)
(The Metropolitan Police Department has not yet announced it)The data has been falsified
(警视厅目前尚未对外发表)资料被窜改了
Did Union do it?
是Union做的吗
Yes, master
是主人
(Frank, you have had a long day, master) I felt this email not quite right…
(弗兰克, 辛苦啦 主人)这邮件怎么感觉不太对劲…
It's just you
就是你吧
A newcomer to the special security department
刚进特殊警备部门的新人
Now that it was the person brought by the chairman
既然是那个理事长带来的人
You must be a good guy
你一定是好人
Is that guy so trusted
那家伙这么受到信赖吗
At least he is the person who founded this school
至少他是创立这所学校的人
Here is a good place
这里是个好地方喔
A good place, really?
好地方…是吗
Is it true or false
真的假的
Go and have a look
去看看吧
What's going on
什么事
Isn't it this guy?
不是这家伙吧
Hey, here is a kid in red hair
喂, 这里有个红发小鬼吧
Come out quickly
还不快出来
You are so cute
妳长得挺可爱的
Let go of me
请放开我
I'm gonna make your friend cry
你的朋友快被我弄哭了
Hurry up and bring people to me
快点把人给我带来
I can't show up because I am staying away from trouble
我在避风头不能露面
Don't get me into trouble
别给我找麻烦啊
Newcomer, please report quickly
新来的, 什么情况快点报告
Sorry, send some people to support
抱歉, 快派人来支援
I can't move now
我现在动不了
Let go of that kid
放开那孩子
No vehicles are allowed in or out here
这里禁止车辆进出
Vehicles in and out in other places
车辆进出口在其他地方
Could you move your car
能不能麻烦你移一下车…
Please leave
请离开
Here is the school
这里是学校
The kids will...
孩子们会…
That's it
这样啊
Is it you?
就是你吗
A brat who bothers other people's women
对别人的女人出手的臭小鬼
Little Yu
小裕
Did you do anything to that woman?
你对那个女人做了什么吗
Before I met you this morning
早上跟你会合之前
Dangerous
危险
Are you all right
妳没事吧
That's all
就这样吗
Please say something good for me
妳也帮我说句话吧
Hey, man
喂, 大叔
Don't be so angry with such trivial things
不要因为这种小事
OK?
就生气到不行好吗
Think of your age
也不想想你都几岁了
What are you doing, man?
大哥你在做什么
Just let him remember that it can never do anything bad again
就让他的身体好好记住再也不可以做坏事吧
Man, you better be a little measured
大叔, 你最好有点分寸
It's too much to be jealous
吃醋吃成这样也太过头了吧
Don't be in your glory
少得意忘形
You are a brat
你这个臭小鬼
Little Yu
小裕
Why do you look at me with that look in your eyes?
为什么用那种眼神看我
Is he instigating me?
他是在指使我吗
Are you kidding
开什么玩笑
I can't go over and make things complicated
我可不能过去把事情闹大
Great
打得好
I will no longer be merciful
我不会再手下留情了
I will kill you
我要宰了你
Little Yu
小裕
Don't be violent against students
不要对学生使用暴力
The janitor
校工伯伯
There is no good end being a good guy
当好人可没什么好下场喔
Let go of him
放开他
Man
叔叔
Here is another yes-man
又来了一个滥好人
Do you want me to repeat this word several times?
一句话要让我说几次
I told you to let go of him
我叫你放开他
Man, go aside
大叔给我一边凉快去
You guy
你这家伙
How can it be?
这怎么可能
You actually didn't move
居然动也不动
If no one else was watching
要是没有其他人在看
you would have died long ago
你早就死了
Both of you, hurry up and go
你们两个, 快走
Man
叔叔
Thank you, man
谢谢你, 叔叔
You are terribly strong
你强得吓死人了
You were really good just now
刚才真的很厉害
So gorgeous
好帅喔
Are you practicing pedro fleitas?
你有在练格斗技吗
That's awesome
好厉害
We were born in a transparent glass tube
我们在透明的玻璃管中出生
and didn't make much contribution since birth
活着没做出什么贡献
Our bodies were exposed
身体被暴露在外
and our blood was drawn
被抽取血液
Our lives were discarded after being utilized
我们的生命被利用后就被丢弃
It was finally useful
好不容易有点用处
But we even don't have a formal name
却连个正式的名字都没有
We were the only people who have survived to identify with ourselves
活下来认同自己的人只有彼此
Everyone desperately wanted to survive
大家却拼命的想活下来
Just like ordinary humans living in this city
就像住在这城市的平凡人类一样
We are ordinary
平凡啊
You are right
说得也对
That's life  for granted
这是理所当然的人生
Let's find our names together
我们一起找名字吧
We will find our names some day
总有一天要找出我们的名字
And the names of the dead partners
还有死去的那些伙伴的名字
I heard about the school
学校的事情我听说了
Sorry, I was too rash
抱歉, 是我太轻率了
I hid here with the help of your power
我可是借用你的力量才能躲藏在此
Remember not to kill people, and be merciful sometimes
记得别把人杀了, 适当的手下留情
Actually, I don’t need to say much
其实也不用我多说
I have one thing I must do
我有一件非做不可的事情
I must complete my agreement with my partner
我必须完成我和伙伴的约定
Could I leave here?
能不能让我留在这里
Please
拜托你
What are you talking about?
你在说什么啊
I said you can stay here
我原本就说你可以留下来
What's your opinion?
你有什么看法
Master
主人您决定将他留在这里的理由
I seem to understand the reason why you decided to let him stay here
属下似乎能理解了
M-24, I must definitely fulfill the agreement
M-24, 我一定会实现约定
Before that day
在那一天来之前
I will live an ordinary and natural life with you
我就和你们一起过平凡又理所当然的人生
Here is Japan
这里就是日本
a big city
是大城市
Want me to make a show of strength in such a place?
要我在这种地方发威吗
The task this time is not war
这次的任务不是战争
Is it a terrorist act?
是进行恐怖行动吧
No
不
The task this time is not to fight but to investigate
这次的任务不是战斗而是调查
Investigation
调查
Jack and Mary in charge of recycling the coffin
负责棺木回收任务的杰克和玛丽
They cannot be contacted in this country
在这个国家断了音信
They actually…
他们居然…
The two failed subjects also disappeared
那两个失败的实验体也不知去向
I hacked into organization's computer to get this information while I was killing time
这是我打发时间时骇进组织的电脑查到的情报
But why did they let us investigate it
不过为什么让我们调查
Is it necessary to use us for this job, reinforced for the big battle?
这工作有必要出动专为大型战斗而强化的我们吗
It doesn't matter
无所谓
We are only responsible for following the orders of the organization
我们只负责遵从组织的命令